[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", ":", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "And the gap between those two positions in the public estimation, I guess in your own estimation is just so massive, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "gap", "between", "those", "two", "positions", "in", "the", "public", "estimation", ",", "I", "guess", "in", "your", "own", "estimation", "is", "just", "so", "massive", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I think people don't really -- it's hard for people to grasp the -- everything that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "people", "do", "n't", "really", "--", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "people", "to", "grasp", "the", "--", "everything", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "So -- I mean even now are they aware of what happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "--", "I", "mean", "even", "now", "are", "they", "aware", "of", "what", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "No, they're not aware.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "aware", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "How intoxicating is that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "intoxicating", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "ONES: Incredibly.", "answer_tokens": ["ONES", ":", "Incredibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "Because you didn't want to hear it?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "you", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "hear", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Twenty-three?", "question_tokens": ["Twenty-three", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Yes, I mean, but even -- even before then, at the age of 15, I made my first Olympic team, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "but", "even", "--", "even", "before", "then", ",", "at", "the", "age", "of", "15", ",", "I", "made", "my", "first", "Olympic", "team", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 137, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "-- it's -- it's the reality check --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "the", "reality", "check", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marion Jones"]}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "What did you learn about yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, I -- I -- I realized that -- that my priorities were totally out of whack and that -- that I had to figure out who I was, not Marion Jones, the superstar athlete, the pretty smile, the charm and all that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "--", "I", "realized", "that", "--", "that", "my", "priorities", "were", "totally", "out", "of", "whack", "and", "that", "--", "that", "I", "had", "to", "figure", "out", "who", "I", "was", ",", "not", "Marion", "Jones", ",", "the", "superstar", "athlete", ",", "the", "pretty", "smile", ",", "the", "charm", "and", "all", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Appalling painful though it is, that's the beginning of the moving on process, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Appalling", "painful", "though", "it", "is", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "beginning", "of", "the", "moving", "on", "process", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "It was.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "-- and look her in the eye and say, it's true?", "question_tokens": ["--", "and", "look", "her", "in", "the", "eye", "and", "say", ",", "it", "'s", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Oh, extremely painful, because, you know, she was and still is my biggest support.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "extremely", "painful", ",", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "she", "was", "and", "still", "is", "my", "biggest", "support", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Did you turn to her, having rejected her in the way that you said you did -- what was the moment you turned back to her?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "turn", "to", "her", ",", "having", "rejected", "her", "in", "the", "way", "that", "you", "said", "you", "did", "--", "what", "was", "the", "moment", "you", "turned", "back", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", ",", "VBG", "VBN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Not too long after I -- after I pled guilty.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "too", "long", "after", "I", "--", "after", "I", "pled", "guilty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Because your mother, I guess, had lived the great highs?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "your", "mother", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "had", "lived", "the", "great", "highs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Was she angry with you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "angry", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "What was the poorest choice your mother thinks you ever made?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "poorest", "choice", "your", "mother", "thinks", "you", "ever", "made", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Well, certainly my decision in men.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "my", "decision", "in", "men", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Why were you attracted to the bad guys?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "attracted", "to", "the", "bad", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I don't know, I think I saw -- I saw something in them that perhaps I was lacking in my childhood.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "I", "think", "I", "saw", "--", "I", "saw", "something", "in", "them", "that", "perhaps", "I", "was", "lacking", "in", "my", "childhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Do you have any relationship with him at all?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "relationship", "with", "him", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 237, "question": "So you -- you were craving a kind of father substitute, possibly?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "--", "you", "were", "craving", "a", "kind", "of", "father", "substitute", ",", "possibly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 238, "answer": "Possibly.", "answer_tokens": ["Possibly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Is he still alive, your biological father?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "still", "alive", ",", "your", "biological", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "No, he's passed.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "passed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Did you have any feelings about that when you heard?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "feelings", "about", "that", "when", "you", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Not -- but not having a strong male presence in your life and all the pressure on your mom to bring you up and everything, it can't help, can it?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "--", "but", "not", "having", "a", "strong", "male", "presence", "in", "your", "life", "and", "all", "the", "pressure", "on", "your", "mom", "to", "bring", "you", "up", "and", "everything", ",", "it", "ca", "n't", "help", ",", "can", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "ONES: No.", "answer_tokens": ["ONES", ":", "No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "I mean it's like a shark pool, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "'s", "like", "a", "shark", "pool", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "But by the time the child is old enough and go off to college, how much protecting can you do?", "question_tokens": ["But", "by", "the", "time", "the", "child", "is", "old", "enough", "and", "go", "off", "to", "college", ",", "how", "much", "protecting", "can", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Let's take another break.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "take", "another", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Can we get there quick, please?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "get", "there", "quick", ",", "please", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "We can get there reasonably quick.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "can", "get", "there", "reasonably", "quick", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "And you'd gone from 80,000 dollars a race?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'d", "gone", "from", "80,000", "dollars", "a", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["80,000 dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Your kids went to stay with your family in Barbados, right?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "kids", "went", "to", "stay", "with", "your", "family", "in", "Barbados", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Correct.", "answer_tokens": ["Correct", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Barbados"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "Would you have still won the gold?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "still", "won", "the", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Can I play Devil's Advocate with you?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "play", "Devil", "'s", "Advocate", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Is that the honest truth?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "honest", "truth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "That moment, when you hand back the medals and you hear this guy say that about you and that is how you're being branded to America, how did that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["That", "moment", ",", "when", "you", "hand", "back", "the", "medals", "and", "you", "hear", "this", "guy", "say", "that", "about", "you", "and", "that", "is", "how", "you", "'re", "being", "branded", "to", "America", ",", "how", "did", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Well, I didn't -- it -- it was tough to hand back the medals, certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "--", "it", "--", "it", "was", "tough", "to", "hand", "back", "the", "medals", ",", "certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "-- what might have been?", "question_tokens": ["--", "what", "might", "have", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "CC", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Or is tempted?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "is", "tempted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "-- keeping it secret or is tempted to or believes it's the only way they can win a gold medal --", "answer_tokens": ["--", "keeping", "it", "secret", "or", "is", "tempted", "to", "or", "believes", "it", "'s", "the", "only", "way", "they", "can", "win", "a", "gold", "medal", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "-- there's nobody better to ask, what -- what advice would you give them?", "question_tokens": ["--", "there", "'s", "nobody", "better", "to", "ask", ",", "what", "--", "what", "advice", "would", "you", "give", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "JJR", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", ":", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "First of all, think about the consequences of your choices.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "think", "about", "the", "consequences", "of", "your", "choices", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "How does it feel for you going back on tour, on the road and Michael's no longer here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "it", "feel", "for", "you", "going", "back", "on", "tour", ",", "on", "the", "road", "and", "Michael", "'s", "no", "longer", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Well, we miss him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "miss", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marlon"]}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "And Tito, how do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Tito", ",", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, I agree with Marlon with what he was saying.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "agree", "with", "Marlon", "with", "what", "he", "was", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 447, "question": "Six shows a day?", "question_tokens": ["Six", "shows", "a", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 448, "answer": "Six shows a day.", "answer_tokens": ["Six", "shows", "a", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "See what is abnormal?", "question_tokens": ["See", "what", "is", "abnormal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Well, that's a very good point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "very", "good", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Or do you now -- now that you are older and you have had kids, some of you yourselves, do you get it?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "do", "you", "now", "--", "now", "that", "you", "are", "older", "and", "you", "have", "had", "kids", ",", "some", "of", "you", "yourselves", ",", "do", "you", "get", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I get it totally.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "get", "it", "totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "When you say that -- as you sit here now, you're all in your late 50s, 60 in one -- you are the oldest right?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "say", "that", "--", "as", "you", "sit", "here", "now", ",", "you", "'re", "all", "in", "your", "late", "50s", ",", "60", "in", "one", "--", "you", "are", "the", "oldest", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", ",", "CD", "IN", "CD", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I'm the oldest.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "the", "oldest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "How old are you, 60, 61?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "are", "you", ",", "60", ",", "61", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "Sixty one.", "answer_tokens": ["Sixty", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "How do you get along with him now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "along", "with", "him", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Very well.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "RB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Did you worry that it was too much for one person to take?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "worry", "that", "it", "was", "too", "much", "for", "one", "person", "to", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "We had worries about just -- later during the circle of people, but not so much of what he was achieving.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "worries", "about", "just", "--", "later", "during", "the", "circle", "of", "people", ",", "but", "not", "so", "much", "of", "what", "he", "was", "achieving", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "I mean, how did you feel as brothers?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "how", "did", "you", "feel", "as", "brothers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Well, I was wondering how he was going to do 50 dates, first of all.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "wondering", "how", "he", "was", "going", "to", "do", "50", "dates", ",", "first", "of", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did you feel he was OK and himself?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "he", "was", "OK", "and", "himself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "UH", "CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I thought he was fine, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "he", "was", "fine", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "What do you feel, Tito, about Conrad Murray?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", ",", "Tito", ",", "about", "Conrad", "Murray", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Well, I feel that -- like we're supposed to have forgiving hearts.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "feel", "that", "--", "like", "we", "'re", "supposed", "to", "have", "forgiving", "hearts", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tito", "Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Do you forgive him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "forgive", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "Sure, I forgive him.", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", ",", "I", "forgive", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Do you all feel that way?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "all", "feel", "that", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "You don't, Jermaine?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", ",", "Jermaine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "No, I don't feel that way at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "feel", "that", "way", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jermaine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What do you feel?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I feel like it's just negligence and not on his -- it's on his part plus others.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "it", "'s", "just", "negligence", "and", "not", "on", "his", "--", "it", "'s", "on", "his", "part", "plus", "others", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "The accusations, The molestation charge, all that kind of thing, did it have a very bad impact on him, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["The", "accusations", ",", "The", "molestation", "charge", ",", "all", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", ",", "did", "it", "have", "a", "very", "bad", "impact", "on", "him", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "\"Shake Your Body\"?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Shake", "Your", "Body", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "Do you ever have arguments?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "have", "arguments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "Who would win if you were to fight?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "win", "if", "you", "were", "to", "fight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "I would.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", "''", "CC", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Tito?", "question_tokens": ["Tito", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "I like the old stuff, like \"I Want You Back\" and \"ABC,\" \"The Love You Save,\" the Motown stuff.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "the", "old", "stuff", ",", "like", "``", "I", "Want", "You", "Back", "''", "and", "``", "ABC", ",", "''", "``", "The", "Love", "You", "Save", ",", "''", "the", "Motown", "stuff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "All the hits?", "question_tokens": ["All", "the", "hits", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "How are you going to commemorate Michael on tour, in terms of the actual tour, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "commemorate", "Michael", "on", "tour", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "the", "actual", "tour", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "I don't think you really can.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "really", "can", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "The hologram thing is a rumor that's not true?", "question_tokens": ["The", "hologram", "thing", "is", "a", "rumor", "that", "'s", "not", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "Here's what happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "what", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 744, "question": "You started all that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "started", "all", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 745, "answer": "He started all that.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "started", "all", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120527pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "Can we bring you on the stage?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "bring", "you", "on", "the", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]